Guide to the Syria Collection of photographs AD.MC.036
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Vernacular Series (Box 4)
  - A group portrait of two men in suits, one is wearing guthrah (linked ref 655)., Circa 1955-1975; ref663; Studio Tuni and Safar, Entree de Rue Fardoss, Côté de Tour D'Argent, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria; Men; Forest/Woodlands; Regional/National Dress; Outdoors; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of several men standing around a table., Circa 1955-1975; ref664; Studio Tuni and Safar, Entree de Rue Fardoss, Côté de Tour D'Argent, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Damascus, Syria; Food; Men; Gatherings; Regional/National Dress; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - A group portrait of five men in front of a couch., Circa 1955-1975; ref665; Studio Tuni and Safar, Entree de Rue Fardoss, Côté de Tour D'Argent, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Men; Clocks/Watches; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of four men, one holds a camera, and two touch one man's stomach., Circa 1955-1975; ref666; Studio Tuni and Safar, Entree de Rue Fardoss, Côté de Tour D'Argent, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Men; Cameras; Cars/Trucks; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Damascus, Syria; Transportation; Facial Hair; Clocks/Watches; Streets/Roads
  - A group portrait of three men standing under an arch (linked ref 650)., Circa 1955-1975; ref667; Studio Tuni and Safar, Entree de Rue Fardoss, Côté de Tour D'Argent, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Men; Cars/Trucks; Cameras; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Damascus, Syria; Transportation
  - A group portrait of four men in an amphitheater (linked ref 653)., Circa 1955-1975; ref668; Studio Tuni and Safar, Entree de Rue Fardoss, Côté de Tour D'Argent, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A group portrait of four men in an amphitheater (linked ref 668)., Circa 1955-1975; ref669; Studio Tuni and Safar, Entree de Rue Fardoss, Côté de Tour D'Argent, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Men; Damascus, Syria; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A group portrait of three men standing under an arch (linked ref 667)., Circa 1955-1975; ref670; Studio Tuni and Safar, Entree de Rue Fardoss, Côté de Tour D'Argent, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Men; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Damascus, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - A monument with three sculptures of people., Circa 1955-1975; ref671; Studio Tuni and Safar, Entree de Rue Fardoss, Côté de Tour D'Argent, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Outdoors; Buildings; Statues/Sculptures; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A woman and man standing in the Cairo Tower, the Maspero television building is in the background., Circa 1965-1975; ref672; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.5 x 12.5 cm (Box 4, Folder NA)
    Women; Buildings; Men; Zamalek/Gezira, Cairo, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Architecture
  - A woman and man standing beside a telescope on the Cairo Tower, the Nile Hilton and Arab League buildings are visible in the background (linked ref 672)., Circa 1965-1975; ref673; 1 Photographic Prints; 17 x 12.1 cm (Box 4, Folder NA)
    Men; Women; Buildings; Zamalek/Gezira, Cairo, Egypt; Telescope; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hotels; Architecture
  - A colorized postcard of Evacuation Place, Aleppo., Circa 1965-1975; ref674; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.1 x 10 cm (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Aleppo, Syria; Postcards; Landscapes; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Mosques; Religious Sites; Mountains/Hills
  - A group portrait of two young boys, one has his arm around the other., 22 April 1965; ref675; 1 Photographic Prints; 13 x 17.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Boys; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Syria; Children
  - A portrait of Fairuz wearing Balenciaga sunglasses., Circa 1965-1975; ref676; 1 Photographic Prints; 12.8 x 18 cm (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Women; Clocks/Watches; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Performing Arts; Jewelry; Arabic Writing
  - An archway of a building's courtyard., Circa 1965-1975; ref677; Photo V. Derounian, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 12.1 x 17 cm (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Architecture; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria; French Writing
  - A portrait of a woman looking sideways., Circa 1965-1975; ref678; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.6 x 12.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - A silhouette of a man with a camera in front of a building with many flags., Circa 1965-1975; ref679; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.8 x 13 cm (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Men; Flags; Buildings; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cameras
  - A studio portrait of a woman in a wedding dress next to a man wearing a suit., Circa 1965-1975; ref680; Rahe, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 21.2 x 17.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Women; Men; Weddings; Head Covers/Veils; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Syria; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - A studio portrait of a woman in a wedding dress., Circa 1965-1975; ref681; Rahe, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 21.3 x 16.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Women; Weddings; Men; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Gloves
  - A studio portrait of a young girl sitting on a chair., Circa 1965-1975; ref682; 1 Photographic Prints; 22.4 x 16.9 cm (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Girls; Children; Furnishings; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A studio envelope from Sarkissian Studio., Circa 1980-1990; ref685; Sarkissian Studio, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.6 x 12.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Damascus, Syria; Printed Materials
  - A studio envelope from Reem Color Studio., Circa 1980-1990; ref686; Reem Color, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 16.5 x 11.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - A studio envelope from Reem Color Studio., Circa 1980-1990; ref687; Reem Color, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.3 x 10.7 cm (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - A studio envelope from Sarkissian Studio., Circa 1980-1990; ref688; Sarkissian Studio, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.7 x 14.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - A studio envelope from Sarkissian Studio., Circa 1980-1990; ref689; Sarkissian Studio, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 19.7 x 12.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - A studio envelope from Reem Color Studio., Circa 1980-1990; ref690; Reem Color, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 19 x 15.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - A studio envelope from Sarkissian Studio., Circa 1980-1990; ref691; Sarkissian Studio, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 17.8 x 11 cm (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - A studio envelope from Sarkissian Studio., Circa 1980-1990; ref692; Sarkissian Studio, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 12.9 x 17 cm (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - A studio envelope from Studio Dunia, Derhagopian., Circa 1960-1975; ref864; Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 16 x 10 cm (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Syria; Printed Materials; Advertisements
- Actor Headshots Series (Box 5)
  - A headshot of an actor dressed in robes., Circa 1950-1975; ref830; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.9 x 18 cm (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Men; Actors; Costumes; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of two men surrounded by stage props., Circa 1950-1975; ref831; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.8 x 18 cm (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Costumes; Actors; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Guns; Weapons; Men; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing
  - An actor headshot of a woman wearing a cross., Circa 1950-1975; ref832; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.9 x 17.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Women; Religious Crosses; Costumes; Actors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A headshot of a male actor., Circa 1950-1975; ref833; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 17.8 cm (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Men; Actors; Costumes; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Arabic Writing
  - A portrait of a male actor in costume., Circa 1950-1975; ref834; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 18.1 cm (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Men; Individual Portraits; Weapons; Costumes; Actors; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Arabic Writing
  - A portrait of a male actor in costume., Circa 1950-1975; ref835; 1 Photographic Prints; 24.2 x 18 cm (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Men; Costumes; Actors; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Costumes
  - A portrait of a male actor., Circa 1950-1975; ref836; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 17.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Men; Costumes; Actors; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria; Arabic Writing
  - A portrait of a male actor in costume., Circa 1950-1975; ref837; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 18.2 cm (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Men; Costumes; Actors; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - A portrait of a female actress., Circa 1950-1975; ref838; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.9 x 18.1 cm (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Women; Hats; Costumes; Actors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing
  - A portrait of a male actor., Circa 1950-1975; ref839; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 17.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Men; Individual Portraits; Actors; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
  - A portrait of a male actor wearing a fez., Circa 1950-1975; ref840; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 17.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Men; Actors; Facial Hair; Fez/Tarboush; Individual Portraits; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a male actor wearing ghutrah., Circa 1960-1975; ref841; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.9 x 17.8 cm (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Men; Actors; Regional/National Dress; Costumes; Facial Hair; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing
  - A portrait of a male actor with his head covered., Circa 1960-1975; ref842; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 17.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Head Covers/Veils; Men; Facial Hair; Arabic Writing; Costumes; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - A portrait of a male actor wearing a fez., Circa 1960-1975; ref843; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 17.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Men; Facial Hair; Fez/Tarboush; Actors; Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of a male actor wearing ghutrah., Circa 1960-1975; ref844; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 17.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Costumes; Regional/National Dress; Men; Actors; Facial Hair; Individual Portraits; Syria; Arabic Writing
  - A portrait of a male actor in costume., Circa 1960-1975; ref845; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 17.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Men; Actors; Costumes; Individual Portraits; Syria; Arabic Writing
  - A portrait of a male actor with his head covered., Circa 1960-1975; ref846; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 17.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Head Covers/Veils; Men; Actors; Costumes; Syria; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A portrait of a male actor in costume., Circa 1960-1975; ref847; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 17.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Men; Actors; Costumes; Syria; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of a male actor in costume., Circa 1960-1975; ref848; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 18 cm (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Men; Costumes; Syria; Actors; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
  - A portrait of a female actress., Circa 1960-1975; ref849; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 18 cm (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Women; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Actors
  - A portrait of a male actor., Circa 1960-1975; ref850; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 17.8 cm (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Men; Actors; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Syria
  - A group portrait of two actors dressed in military uniforms., Circa 1960-1975; ref851; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.7 x 17.8 cm (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Costumes; Actors; Men; Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
  - A portrait of a male actor., Circa 1960-1975; ref852; Ministry of Culture, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 17.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Men; Actors; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a male actor in costume., Circa 1960-1975; ref853; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.8 x 18 cm (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Men; Actors; Costumes; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Arabic Writing
  - A portrait of a male actor in costume., Circa 1960-1975; ref854; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.8 x 18 cm (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Men; Costumes; Actors; Syria; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
  - A portrait of a male actor in costume., Circa 1960-1975; ref855; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.8 x 18 cm (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Men; Costumes; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Actors; Syria; Arabic Writing
  - A group portrait of two actors and a veiled actress., Circa 1960-1975; ref856; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.9 x 18.1 cm (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Men; Women; Actors; Costumes; Regional/National Dress; Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a man composed of the bodies of women., Circa 1960-1975; ref857; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.8 x 9 cm (Box 5, Folder 14)
    Men; Women; Art; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of three men in military uniforms., Circa 1965-1975; ref684; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.8 x 17.9 cm (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Guns; Weapons; Damascus, Syria; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Costumes; Facial Hair; Actors
  - A group portrait of a veiled woman and two men., Circa 1965-1975; ref683; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.8 x 17.9 cm (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Men; Women; Canes/Walking Sticks; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Costumes; Facial Hair; Actors
- Party Series (Box 5)
  - a group portrait of four women eating and smoking (linked ref816)., Circa 1940-1965; ref815; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Women; Food; Jewelry; Smoking; Parties; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of three women (linked ref815)., Circa 1940-1965; ref816; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Men; Women; Parties; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several people around a set table., Circa 1940-1965; ref817; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.6 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Men; Women; Regional/National Dress; Drinks/Beverages; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Parties; Syria
  - A group portrait of a man and a woman (linked ref819)., Circa 1940-1965; ref818; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Men; Women; Drinks/Beverages; Parties; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of a man and a woman (linked ref818)., Circa 1940-1965; ref819; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 6.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Men; Women; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Parties; Syria
  - A group portrait of several women sitting on a couch (linked ref821)., Circa 1940-1965; ref820; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.6 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Women; Group Portraits; Syria; Parties; Photographic Prints
  - A group portrait of several women sitting on a couch (linked ref820)., Circa 1940-1965; ref821; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 6.9 cm (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Women; Syria; Parties; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several men and a woman around a table., Circa 1940-1965; ref822; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Men; Smoking; Regional/National Dress; Women; Photographic Prints; Syria; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Parties
  - A group portrait of two men and one woman., Circa 1940-1965; ref823; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Men; Facial Hair; Women; Parties; Syria; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of two men and a girl., Circa 1940-1965; ref824; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Men; Girls; Children; Parties; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several people around a table., Circa 1940-1965; ref825; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.6 x 7.5 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - A group portrait of five people sitting on a couch., Circa 1940-1965; ref826; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 6.2 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Men; Women; Girls; Children; Syria; Parties; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of several women and children inside., Circa 1940-1965; ref827; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Girls; Children; Men; Photographic Prints; Parties; Women; Syria; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of a man and a woman (linked ref819)., Circa 1940-1965; ref828; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - A group portrait of two women and a man (linked ref828)., Circa 1940-1965; ref829; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.1 x 6.7 cm (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Men; Women; Parties; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits
- Aleppo Series (Box 6)
  - An aerial landscape of a village., Circa 1930-1950; ref890; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Aleppo, Syria; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref891; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.8 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings
  - An aerial landscape of a village., Circa 1930-1950; ref892; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 8.4 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Airplanes; Aleppo, Syria; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of several men and a woman looking out over a city., Circa 1930-1950; ref893; 1 Photographic Prints; 12.4 x 8.4 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Men; Women; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Uniforms
  - An aerial landscape of a village., Circa 1930-1950; ref894; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 x 8.2 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Airplanes; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - A group portrait of several men looking at the ground, taken from a rocky interior., Circa 1930-1950; ref895; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Caves; Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial photo of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref896; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref897; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.7 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints
  - A portrait of a man on horseback., Circa 1930-1950; ref898; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Animals; Horses; Men; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref899; 1 Photographic Prints; 11 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref900; 1 Photographic Prints; 11 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref901; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 x 8.3 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Buildings; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape of a village., Circa 1930-1950; ref902; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.1 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Airplanes; Buildings; Aleppo, Syria
  - A landscape of mountains with a tree in the foreground., Circa 1930-1950; ref903; 1 Photographic Prints; 11 x 8.4 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Aleppo, Syria
  - An aerial landscape of a village., Circa 1930-1950; ref904; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - A landscape of mountains and a body of water., Circa 1930-1950; ref905; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Mountains/Hills; Water; Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - An aerial photo of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref906; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 8.3 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Aleppo, Syria; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Airplanes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial photo of the Citadel of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref907; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Airplanes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Citadel of Aleppo
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref908; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.9 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Landscapes; Airplanes
  - An aerial landscape., Circa 1930-1950; ref909; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 8 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of men conversing in a car., Circa 1930-1950; ref910; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 7.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Cars/Trucks; Men; Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints
  - An aerial landscape of Aleppo., Circa 1930-1950; ref911; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.2 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Buildings; Aleppo, Syria; Airplanes; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A group portrait of a man and a woman outdoors., Circa 1930-1950; ref912; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 x 8.1 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Men; Women; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a man (linked ref912)., Circa 1930-1950; ref913; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 x 8.6 cm (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Men; Landscapes; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints